(Cosmonaut:)So I tell my wife,
"Get a dog, don't get a dog.
(Cosmonaut:)I'm not walking it, I'm not feeding it,
I'm not picking up after it."
You know you're gonna wind up
walking it.
(Amy:)I know.
Um, shouldn't you guys be talking
about space stuff instead of dogs?
(Mike:)Dimitri, Froot Loops
would be more comfortable...
(Mike:)...if we talked about space stuff.
(Dimitri:)Okay. I'm going into space.
(Dimitri:)And when I come back,
I have to pick up a poodle crap.
ls that better?
(Howard:)Thanks.
(Howard:)You know, we could always drive
to Vegas and get married.
(Bernadette:)No, isn't that kind of tacky?
(Penny:)I know tons of people
who got married in Vegas.
- Are any of them still married?
- Yeah.